<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2015 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter NG. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm2/tr/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" username="Dogukan &lt;dogukan@live.de&gt;" orig="Call Meter lets you keep an eye on your mobile plans.\n\nIt shows statistics of your calls/sms/txt/data traffic and lets you set limits for each of these plans.\nCall Meter supports a huge amount of billing modes to let you adapt it\'s behaviour to your operators billing.">Call Meter mobil paketlerinizi izlemenizi sağlar.\n\nGörüşme/sms/data trafiklerinizin istatistiklerini ve her biri için limit belirleme imkanı sunar.\nCall Meter ile bir çok faturalandırma seçeneklerine sahip olarak kullandığınız tarife veya paketi en akıllı şekilde takip edin.</string>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" username="bluesman80@gmail.com" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in market won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website.">Bu uygulama hiç bir çıkar gözetilmeden sunulan açık kaynak kodlu bir yazılımdır. Olumsuz yorumlar eklemek bu uygulamayı geliştirmeye yardımcı olmaz.\nLütfen uygulama ile ilgili sorunlarınızı uygulama web sitesinde bildirin.</string>
  <string name="market_cm3" formatted="false" username="Dogukan &lt;dogukan@live.de&gt;" orig="There is a complete rebuild Call Meter 3G available in market. It has a huge amount of new features like widgets and alerts.\nIt\'s new architecure allows more complex plans.\nFeel free to test it and help me make it more userfriendly as it is currently. ;)">Çeşitli widget ve uyarılar gibi bir çok özelliğe sahip olan Call Meter 3G yeniden ve tamamen geliştirilerek markette kullanıma sunuldu. \nYeni mimarisi daha detaylı ve karmaşık planlarınız için geliştirildi.\nLütfen hepimize ait olan bu açık kaynak uygulamayı sınayarak şimdikinden daha fazla kullanıcı dostu olmasına katkıda bulunun. ;)</string>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" username="Dogukan &lt;dogukan@live.de&gt;" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: http://ub0r.de/translate/cm2/">Dilerseniz bu uygulamanın kendi dilinizdeki çevirisine katkıda bulunabilirsiniz:\nhttp://ub0r.de/translate/cm2/</string>
  <string name="market_website" formatted="false" username="bluesman80@gmail.com" orig="Please see https://github.com/felixb/callmeter/issues for issues and enhancement requests.">Geliştirme talepleri ve sorunlar için lütfen https://code.google.com/p/callmeter/issues/list adresini ziyaret edin.</string>
</resources>
