<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2015 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter NG. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit https://crowdin.com/project/callmeter3g/invitehr/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: https://crowdin.com/project/callmeter3g/invite">Slobodno pomognite u prevođenju ove aplikacije na vaš jezik ovdje:\nhttp://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/</string>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" orig="Call Meter 3G is the most complete monitor app for your Android device: It monitors your calls, text messages and data usage.\n\nIt shows statistics of your usage and shows alerts if you reach your limit.\nThere are all kinds of widgets to show the most valuable statistics directly on the home screen.\n\nCall Meter 3G has a complex rule engine to let you set up the app exactly the way your provider writes your bills.\n\nKnown problems:\n* Viber calls are detected as standard calls. Please tell Viber to fix this.\n* Doesn\'t count properly data usage on some Samsung devices. This problem is based on Samsung\'s Android version and got fixed on most devices with some Android update." username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;">Call Meter vam omogućuje držati vašu mobilnu potrošnju na oku.\n\nPokazuje statistike vaših poziva/SMS/txt/podatkovnog prometa i omogućuje vam postavljanje granica za svaki od tih troškova.\nCall Meter podržava golemi broj načina naplate kako bi ga mogli prilagoditi načinu obračuna vašeg operatera.\n\n\nPoznati problemi:\n* Viber pozive detektira kao standardne pozive. Molim vas prijavite Viberu da to poprave.\n* Ne broji točno potrošnju mobilne veze kod nekih Samsungovih uređaja. Taj problem je baziran na Samsungovoj Android inačici i popravljen je na većini uređaja sa Android aktualizacijom.\n</string>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in Play Store won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website." username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;">Ovo je aplikacija otvorenog koda koja se radi u slobodno vrijeme. Dodavanje loših komentara na marketu neće pomoći da bude bolja.\nMolimo navedite svoje probleme s ovom aplikacijom na web stranici aplikacije.</string>
  <string name="market_cm2" formatted="false" orig="This is a complete rebuild of Call Meter NG. It has a huge amount of new features like widgets and alerts.\nIt\'s new architecure allows more complex plans.\nFeel free to test it and help me make it more userfriendly as it is currently. ;)">Ovo je potpuno obnovljeni Call Meter NG. Sadrži golemu količinu novih značajki kao što su dodaci i upozorenja.\nOvo je nova arhitektura koja omogućuje složenije planove.\nSlobodno testirajte i pomognite mi učiniti aplikaciju korisnijom nego što je trenutno. ;)</string>
  <string name="market_permissions" formatted="false" username="grmone.pu@gmail.com" orig="Permissions of this app:\n* READ SMS OR MMS: count your messages\n* RECEIVE SMS: update logs before a recently received message got deleted\n* FULL INTERNET ACCESS: importing rules\n* READ CONTACT DATA: convert numbers to names (e.g. in number groups)\n* MODIFY/DELETE SD CARD CONTENTS: write/export rules to sd card\n* READ PHONE STATE AND IDENTITY: update logs in background\n* PREVENT DEVICE FROM SLEEPING: update logs in background">Dopuštenja za ovu aplikaciju\n* ČITANJE SMS ILI MMS: broji vaše poruke\n* PRIMLJENI SMS: ažurira zapisnik prije nego što primljena poruka bude obrisana\n* POTPUNI PRISTUP INTERNETU: uvoz pravila\n* ČITANJE KONTAKATA: pretvaranje brojeva u imena (npr. u grupi brojeva)\n* IZMJENA/BRISANJE SADRŽAJA SD KARTICE: pisanje/izvoz pravila na sd karticu\n* ČITANJE STANJA TELEFONA I IDENTITETA: ažuriranje zapisnika u pozadini\n* SPRJEČAVANJE UREĐAJA DA ODE U SLEEP NAČIN: ažuriranje zapisnika u pozadini</string>
  <string name="market_promo" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Never spend too much!">Nikad ne potrošite previše!</string>
  <string name="market_website" formatted="false" username="Grmone&lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Please see https://github.com/felixb/callmeter/issues for issues and enhancement requests.">Molim Vas pogledajte https://github.com/felixb/callmeter/issues za pitanja i pojašnjavanja zahtjeva.</string>
</resources>
