<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
		Copyright (C) 2009-2013 Felix Bechstein
	-->
<!--
		This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you
		can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU
		General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation;
		either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later
		version.
	-->
<!--
		This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
		WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
		MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
		General Public License for more details. You should have received a
		copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
		not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
	-->
<resources>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" username="Igor Kutlarevic &lt;kuxman_ns@yahoo.com&gt;" orig="Call Meter 3G is the most complete monitor app for your Android device: It monitors your calls, text messages and data usage.\n\nIt shows statistics of your usage and shows alerts if you reach your limit.\nThere are all kinds of widgets to show the most valuable statistics directly on the home screen.\n\nCall Meter 3G has a complex rule engine to let you set up the app exactly the way your provider writes your bills.\n\nKnown problems:\n* Viber calls are detected as standard calls. Please tell Viber to fix this.\n* Doesn\'t count properly data usage on some Samsung devices. This problem is based on Samsung\'s Android version and got fixed on most devices with some Android update.">Call Meter 3G je najkompletnija aplikacija za Vaš Android koja vam omogućava da pratite pozive, poruke i korišćenje interneta.\n\nPokazuje statistike korišćenja telefona i omogućava vam postavljanje granica za svaki od tih troškova.\nPomoću različitih widgeta, pokazuje vam statistiku direktno na početnom ekranu.\n\nCall Meter 3G sadrži kompleksan engine kako bi podesili aplikaciju tačno onako kako Vam vaš provajder ispostavlja račun.\n\nPostojeći problemi:\n* Viber pozivi se računaju kao standardni pozivi. Molimo obratite se Viber-u kako bi to popravio.\n* Na nekim Samsung modelima merenje količine internet podataka se ne prikazuje pravilno. Problem je u verziji Androida za Samsung i popravljen je na većini modela sa novijim update-om.</string>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" username="Igor Kutlarevic &lt;kuxman_ns@yahoo.com&gt;" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in Play Store won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website.">Ovo je aplikacija otvorenog koda koja je rađena u autorovo slobodno vreme. Dodavanje loših komentara u Play Store-u neće pomoći da bude bolja.\nMolimo, navedite svoje probleme s ovom aplikacijom na web stranici aplikacije.</string>
  <string name="market_cm2" formatted="false" username="Igor Kutlarevic &lt;kuxman_ns@yahoo.com&gt;" orig="This is a complete rebuild of Call Meter NG. It has a huge amount of new features like widgets and alerts.\nIt\'s new architecure allows more complex plans.\nFeel free to test it and help me make it more userfriendly as it is currently. ;)">Ovo je potpuno obnovljeni Call Meter 3G/NG. Sadrži ogromnu količinu novih dodataka kao što su widgeti i upozorenja.\nOva nova arhitektura omogućava složenije planove.\nSlobodno testirajte i pomozite mi učiniti aplikaciju korisnijom nego što je trenutno. ;)</string>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" username="Igor Kutlarevic &lt;kuxman_ns@yahoo.com&gt;" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: https://crowdin.com/project/callmeter3g/invite">Slobodno pomozite u prevođenju ove aplikacije na vaš jezik ovde:\nhttp://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/</string>
  <string name="market_permissions" formatted="false" username="Igor Kutlarevic &lt;kuxman_ns@yahoo.com&gt;" orig="Permissions of this app:\n* READ SMS OR MMS: count your messages\n* RECEIVE SMS: update logs before a recently received message got deleted\n* FULL INTERNET ACCESS: importing rules\n* READ CONTACT DATA: convert numbers to names (e.g. in number groups)\n* MODIFY/DELETE SD CARD CONTENTS: write/export rules to sd card\n* READ PHONE STATE AND IDENTITY: update logs in background\n* PREVENT DEVICE FROM SLEEPING: update logs in background">Dopuštenja za ovu aplikaciju\n* ČITANJE SMS-a ILI MMS-a: broji vaše poruke\n* PRIMLJENI SMS: ažurira zapisnik pre nego što primljena poruka bude obrisana\n* POTPUNI PRISTUP INTERNETU: uvoz pravila\n* ČITANJE KONTAKATA: pretvaranje brojeva u imena (npr. u grupi brojeva)\n* IZMENA/BRISANJE SADRŽAJA SD KARTICE: pisanje/izvoz pravila na sd karticu\n* ČITANJE STANJA TELEFONA I IDENTITETA: ažuriranje zapisnika u pozadini\n* SPREČAVANJE UREĐAJA DA ODE U SLEEP MOD: ažuriranje zapisnika u pozadini</string>
  <string name="market_website" formatted="false" username="Igor Kutlarevic &lt;kuxman_ns@yahoo.com&gt;" orig="Please see https://github.com/felixb/callmeter/issues for issues and enhancement requests.">Molimo pogledajte https://github.com/felixb/callmeter/issues za pitanja i pojašnjenja zahteva.</string>
  <string name="market_promo" formatted="false" username="Igor Kutlarevic &lt;kuxman_ns@yahoo.com&gt;" orig="Never spend too much!">Nikada ne potrošite previše!</string>
</resources>
