<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2013 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/pt/help.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="help_title_" formatted="false" username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Please read the following to understand the concept of &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Leia os elementos seguintes para perceber os conceitos de <b>registos</b>, <b>planos</b> e <b>regras</b>:</string>
  <string name="help_import_" formatted="false" username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;" orig="A good starting point are some preconfigured rule sets available on the website. Just import them via import menu and play around.">Aceda ao nosso sítio web para obter diversos conjuntos de regras. Importe-as através do menu e comece já a utilizar.</string>
  <string name="help_export_" formatted="false" orig="If you managed to set up a common plan for your country, do not hesitate to export your rule set to me by mail. I will put it on the website to make it available for all the users." username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;">Se conseguiu configurar um plano recorrente do seu país, envie-o para mim através de correio eletrónico. O plano será colocado no sítio web e ficará disponível para todos os utilizadores.</string>
  <string name="help_logs_plans_rules_" formatted="false" orig="There are three kinds of data structures:" username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;">Existem três tipos de estrutura de dados:</string>
  <string name="help_logs_" formatted="false" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; to save informations about your calls, messages and traffic statistics." username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;"><b>Registos</b> para guardar as informações sobre as chamadas, mensagens e estatísticas de tráfego.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_" formatted="false" orig="&lt;b&gt;Plans&lt;/b&gt; to describe all kinds of aspects of your bill." username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;"><b>Planos</b> para descrever todos os detalhes de faturação..</string>
  <string name="help_rules_" formatted="false" orig="&lt;b&gt;Rules&lt;/b&gt; to match the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a particular &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;." username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;"><b>Regras</b> coincidentes com os <b>registos</b> e para as mover para um <b>plano</b>.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail0_" formatted="false" orig="You can add or delete &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; just as you want. You can set the order by dragging them around with the handle on the right of the list view." username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;">Pode adicionar ou remover tantos <b>planos</b> quantos quiser. Pode definir a sua ordem com o botão existente à direita da vista em lista.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail1_" formatted="false" orig="To edit a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;, you just need to click it. At the next screen, you can set all kind of settings. There are a few, most users won\'t need. But some do. A short help for each setting is displayed in this view. Most settings you do not understand are not used in your country. Just leave them as they are. ;)" username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;">Para editar um <b>plano</b>, basta clicar-lhe. No ecrã seguinte, pode definir as diversas definições. Existem algumas que a maioria dos utilizadores não precisa. É exibida uma pequena ajuda por cada definição exibida nesta vista. Se não entender alguma das regras, o mais provável e que elas não existam no seu país. Deixe-as ficar como estão.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_merge_" formatted="false" orig="You can merge &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; to aggregate their &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; to a combined cost and limit." username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;">Pode unir <b>planos</b> e agregar os seus <b>itens de registo</b> a um plano e limite.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail0_" formatted="false" orig="Edit the &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt; in the same way. Each &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; does match some &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; in which the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; should be billed in." username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;">Edite as <b>regras</b> da mesma forma. Cada <b>regra</b> é coincidente com os <b>itens de registo</b> e podem ser movidos para um <b>plano</b> no qual os <b>registos</b> devem ser faturados.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail1_" formatted="false" orig="But keep in mind, that order is important for &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:" username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;">Mas lembre-se que a ordem é importante para as <b>regras</b>:</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail2_" formatted="false" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; are matched &lt;b&gt;top-down&lt;/b&gt;, means: the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; that matches will stop processing of this particular &lt;b&gt;log item&lt;/b&gt;." username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;">Os <b>registos</b> são comparados de <b>cima para baixo</b>. Isto é: a primeira <b>regra</b> que seja coincidente para o processamento do <b>item de registo</b>.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail3_" formatted="false" orig="E.g.: If you match all calls to 0800% numbers to a \&quot;free\&quot; &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; with the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt;, there is no need to exclude these numbers in the second." username="Sérgio Marques &lt;smarquespt@gmail.com&gt;">Ex.: se você associar todas as chamadas para números 96% a um plano <b>gratuito</b> como primeira regra,não precisa excluir estes números na segunda regra.</string>
</resources>
