<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2011 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/edit.php?lang=pt&file=help.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="help_title_" formatted="false" username="rcp &lt;rhacius@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Please read the following to understand the concept of &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Leia abaixo para entender o conceito de <b>relatórios</b>, <b>planos</b> e <b>regras</b>:</string>
  <string name="help_import_" formatted="false" username="rcp &lt;rhacius@gmail.com&gt;" orig="A good starting point are some preconfigured rule sets available on the website. Just import them via import menu and play around.">Um bom começo é usar as regras pré-configuradas disponível em nosso website.\nApenas importe as regras pelo menu e comece a utilizar.</string>
  <string name="help_export_" formatted="false" orig="If you managed to set up a common plan for your country, do not hesitate to export your rule set to me by mail. I will put it on the website to make it available for all the users.">Se você conseguiu estabelecer um plano comum para o seu país, não hesite em exportar o seu conjunto de regras para mim pelo email. Vou colocá-lo no site para torná-lo disponível para todos os usuários.</string>
  <string name="help_logs_plans_rules_" formatted="false" orig="There are three kinds of data structures:">Existem três tipos de estruturas de dados:</string>
  <string name="help_logs_" formatted="false" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; to save informations about your calls, messages and traffic statistics."><b>Estatísticas</b> para salvar informações sobre as chamadas, mensagens e estatísticas de tráfego.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_" formatted="false" orig="&lt;b&gt;Plans&lt;/b&gt; to describe all kinds of aspects of your bill."><b>Planos</b> para descrever todos os tipos e aspectos de sua conta.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_" formatted="false" orig="&lt;b&gt;Rules&lt;/b&gt; to match the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a particular &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;."><b>Regras</b> que correspondam a um <b>relatório</b> e mover para um <b>plano</b> particular.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail0_" formatted="false" orig="You can add or delete &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; just as you want. You can set the order by dragging them around with the handle on the right of the list view.">Você pode adicionar ou excluir <b>planos</b> como quiser. Você pode definir a ordem, arrastando-os com a alça à direita da lista.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail1_" formatted="false" orig="To edit a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;, you just need to click it. At the next screen, you can set all kind of settings. There are a few, most users won\'t need. But some do. A short help for each setting is displayed in this view. Most settings you do not understand are not used in your country. Just leave them as they are. ;)">Para editar um <b>plano</b>, você só precisa clicar nele. Na próxima tela, você pode definir todos os tipos de configurações. Há alguns, que a maioria dos usuários não irá precisar. Mas alguns fazem. Uma pequena ajuda para cada configuração é exibida. A maioria das configurações que você não entende não são usadas ​​em seu país. Basta deixá-las como elas estão. ;)</string>
  <string name="help_plans_merge_" formatted="false" orig="You can merge &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; to aggregate their &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; to a combined cost and limit.">Você pode mesclar <b>planos</b> para agregar os seus <b>itens log</b> para uma combinação de custos e limites.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail0_" formatted="false" orig="Edit the &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt; in the same way. Each &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; does match some &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; in which the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; should be billed in.">Editar as <b>regras</b> da mesma maneira. Cada <b>regra</b> coincide com alguns  <b>itens log</b> e movê-las para um <b>plano</b> em que os <b>logs</b> devem ser cobrados.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail1_" formatted="false" orig="But keep in mind, that order is important for &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Mas lembre-se, que esta ordem é importante para as <b>regras</b>:</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail2_" formatted="false" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; are matched &lt;b&gt;top-down&lt;/b&gt;, means: the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; that matches will stop processing of this particular &lt;b&gt;log item&lt;/b&gt;."><b>Logs</b> são combinados  de <b>alto-baixo</b>, quer dizer: a primeira <b>regra</b> que corresponde irá parar o processamento deste particular <b>item de log</b>.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail3_" formatted="false" orig="E.g.: If you match all calls to 0800% numbers to a \&quot;free\&quot; &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; with the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt;, there is no need to exclude these numbers in the second.">Ex.: Se você combinar todas as chamadas para números 0800% como <b>plano</b> "gratuito" como <b>primeira</b> regra , não há necessidade de excluir esses números na segunda regra.</string>
</resources>
