<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2012 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/sk/intro.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="intro_" formatted="false" orig="Introducing Call Meter 3G">I would like to express some aicreppation to the writer just for bailing me out of this particular crisis. As a result of scouting throughout the world-wide-web and getting suggestions that were not pleasant, I thought my entire life was over. Existing minus the solutions to the problems you\'ve solved as a result of your good website is a crucial case, as well as those which could have in a wrong way affected my career if I had not noticed your website. The mastery and kindness in dealing with everything was invaluable. I don\'t know what I would\'ve done if I had not discovered such a thing like this. I can also at this moment relish my future. Thanks for your time so much for your specialized and results-oriented help. I won\'t be reluctant to recommend your web blog to anyone who will need direction about this matter.</string>
  <string name="intro0" formatted="false" orig="With &lt;b&gt;Call Meter 3G&lt;/b&gt; you can monitor the usage of your calls, messages and data connections.">S <b>Call Meter 3G</b> môžete sledovať stav vašich hovorov, správ a dátových prenosov.</string>
  <string name="intro1" formatted="false" orig="In order to get accurate statistics, it is important to accurately set Call Meter 3G as they will be billed.">Pre získanie presnej štatistiky, je dôležité správne nastaviť Call Meter 3G podľa vášho vyúčtovania.</string>
  <string name="intro_simple" formatted="false" orig="Most users need only set their settings in menu &lt;b&gt;Basic settings&lt;/b&gt;. Just set the number of inclusive minutes or messages, as well as adjust the cost of calls made, etc..">Väčšina užívateľov potrebuje nastaviť ich nastavenia v menu <b>Základne nastavenia</b>. Stačí nastaviť počet zahŕňajúci minúty alebo správy, rovnako ako upraviť cenu odchádzajúcich hovorov, atď..</string>
  <string name="intro_import" formatted="false" orig="If your billing is more complex, for example because messages and calls are billed as merged units, you can import pre-configured rules. Just select the menu &lt;b&gt;Import rule set&lt;/b&gt;.">Ak je vaša fakturácia zložitejšia, napr. pretože účtovanie správ a hovorov je zlúčené do jedného, môžete vložiť predkonfigurované nastavenie. Len vyberte položku <b>Importovať nastavenie</b></string>
  <string name="intro_export" formatted="false" orig="In any case, when everything is set up, you can export your rules to me. Thus, all other users can benefit from your work.">V každom prípade, ak všetko nastavíte, môžete mi exportovať svoje pravidla. Tak môžu z vašej práce ťažiť aj ostatní užívatelia.</string>
  <string name="intro_recalc0" formatted="false" orig="The statistics are recalculated after each change to the configuration. This will take some time depending on the number of calls or messages and used phone. It therefore makes sense to adjust all the settings possible in one fell swoop.">Štatistické údaje sú prepočítavané po každej zmene v nastavení. To zaberie nejaký čas podle počtu hovorov alebo správ, príp. iného použitia telefónu. Preto se oplatí vykonať všetky možné nastavenia naraz.</string>
  <string name="intro_recalc1" formatted="false" orig="The process can be greatly accelerated by the setting &lt;b&gt;Beginning of recording&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;Delete logs older than&lt;/b&gt;.">Proces môže byť urýchlený nastavením položiek <b>Začiatok záznamu</b> alebo <b>Odstrániť záznamy staršie ako</b></string>
  <string name="intro_data" formatted="false" orig="Please note that no data statistics from before the last phone boot can be displayed.">Pamätajte prosím, že po reštartovaní telefónu nebudú k dispozícii žiadne štatistické údaje.</string>
  <string name="intro_kill" formatted="false" orig="Please note that &lt;b&gt;killing&lt;/b&gt; the app can lead to corrupted (data) statistics.">Pamätajte prosím, že <b>ukončenie</b> aplikácie povedie k nepresným štatistickým údajom.</string>
</resources>
