<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2015 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/iw/help.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="help_title_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Please read the following to understand the concept of &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">אנא קרא את הת המידע הבא כדי להבין את הקונספט של\n<b>logs</b>, <b>plans</b>, <b>rules</b>.</string>
  <string name="help_import_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="A good starting point are some preconfigured rule sets available on the website. Just import them via import menu and play around.">נקודת התחלה טובה היא סטים של כללים שהוגדרו מראש, וזמינים באתר האינטרנט. פשוט ייבא אותם דרך תפריט ייבוא ונסה אותם.</string>
  <string name="help_export_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="If you managed to set up a common plan for your country, do not hesitate to export your rule set to me by mail. I will put it on the website to make it available for all the users.">אם הצלחת להגדיר תכנית פופולרית בארצך, אל תהסס להייצא את סט החוקים אליי בדואר. אני אשים אותם באתר האינטרנט, כדי שיהיו זמינים לכל המשתמשים.</string>
  <string name="help_logs_plans_rules_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="There are three kinds of data structures:">יש שלושה סוגים של מבני נתונים:</string>
  <string name="help_logs_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; to save informations about your calls, messages and traffic statistics."><b>logs</b> כדי לשמור מידע אודות סטטיסטיקה השיחות, ההודעות ותעבורת הנתונים שלך.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Plans&lt;/b&gt; to describe all kinds of aspects of your bill."><b>Plans</b> מתארות את כל סוגי האספקטים של חיובייך.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Rules&lt;/b&gt; to match the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a particular &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;."><b>Rules</b> להתאים ל<b>logs</b> ולהעביר אותם ל<b>plan</b>מסויים</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail0_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="You can add or delete &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; just as you want. You can set the order by dragging them around with the handle on the right of the list view.">באפשרותך לוסיף או למחוק <b>plans</b> כפי שתרצה. תוכל להגדיר סדר בינהן על ידי הזזתם מעלה או מטה בצד ימין של תצוגת הרשימה.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail1_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="To edit a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;, you just need to click it. At the next screen, you can set all kind of settings. There are a few, most users won\'t need. But some do. A short help for each setting is displayed in this view. Most settings you do not understand are not used in your country. Just leave them as they are. ;)">כדי לערוך  <b>plans</b>, פשוט לחץ עליה. במסך הבא, תוכל להגדיר את כל סוגי ההגדרות. חלקן הקטן של ההגדרות לא בשימוש עבור מרבית המשתמשים. עזרה קצרה לכל הגדרה מוצגת בתצוגה זו. רוב ההגדרות שאינך מבין, אינן בשימוש במדינתך. פשוט השאר אותן כפי שהן.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_merge_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="You can merge &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; to aggregate their &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; to a combined cost and limit.">תוכל למזג  <b>plans</b> כדי לאחד את ה<b>log items</b> לחיוב ומגבלה מאוחדים.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail0_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Edit the &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt; in the same way. Each &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; does match some &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; in which the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; should be billed in.">ערוך את ה<b>rules</b> באותה דרך. כל <b>rule</b> מתאים לחלק מ<b>log items</b> ומעביר אותם ל<b>plan</b>  בהן ה<b>logs</b> אמורות להיות מחוייבות.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail1_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="But keep in mind, that order is important for &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">אולם זכור, הסדר חשוב ל<b>rules</b> :</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail2_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; are matched &lt;b&gt;top-down&lt;/b&gt;, means: the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; that matches will stop processing of this particular &lt;b&gt;log item&lt;/b&gt;."><b>logs</b> מותאמות לפי  <b>top-down</b>, כלומר: ה<b>rule</b> הראשון שמתאים, יגרום להפסקת העיבוד של <b>log item</b> מסויים.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail3_" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="E.g.: If you match all calls to 0800% numbers to a \&quot;free\&quot; &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; with the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt;, there is no need to exclude these numbers in the second.">לדוגמה: אם התאמת את כל שיחותיך למספרי 1800% ל <b>plans</b> \"חינם\" ב<b>rule</b> הראשון, אין צורך להחריג את המספרים האלו בכלל השני.</string>
</resources>
