<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2013 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter NG. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit https://crowdin.com/project/callmeter3g/inviteiw/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Call Meter lets you keep an eye on your mobile plans.\n\nIt shows statistics of your calls/sms/txt/data traffic and lets you set limits for each of these plans.\nCall Meter supports a huge amount of billing modes to let you adapt it\'s behaviour to your operators billing.">Call Meter מאפשר לך לעקוב אחר תכניות הסלולר שלך.\n\nהיישום מציג סטטיסטיקות של שיחות, SMS ותעבורת דאטה - ומאפשר לך לקבוע מגבלות לכל אחת מתכניות אלו.\nCall Meter תומך במגוון רב של מצבי חיוב בכדי לתת לך אפשרות להתאימו לתכניות החיוב של המפעיל הסלולרי שלך.</string>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in market won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website.">יישום זה מבוסס קוד פתוח ונבנה על חשבון הזמן הפנוי של המפתח. הוספת הערות רעות במרקט לא יעזרו להפוך אותו לטוב יותר.\nבבקשה הוסף את הקשיים והתקלות שחווית בשימוש ביישום לאתר האינטרנט של היישום.</string>
  <string name="market_cm2" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="This is a complete rebuild of Call Meter NG. It has a huge amount of new features like widgets and alerts.\nIt\'s new architecure allows more complex plans.\nFeel free to test it and help me make it more userfriendly as it is currently. ;)">זוהי בנייה מחדש לחלוטין של Call Meter NG. \nהיישום מכיל כמות רבה של תוספות חדשות כמו ווידג\'טים והתראות.\nהמבנה החדש שלו מאפשר הוספת עוד תכניות מורכבות.\nהרגש חופשי לבחון אותו ולעזור לי לעשות אותו יותר ידידותי למשתמש אף ממה שקיים כעת. ;)</string>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" username="amit&lt;harrisamit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: https://crowdin.com/project/callmeter3g/invite">הרגש חופשי לעזור לתרגם את היישום לשפתך כאן: \nhttp://ub0r.de/translate/cm3</string>
</resources>
