<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2013 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/fr/help.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="help_title_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="Please read the following to understand the concept of &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Lisez ce qui suit pour comprendre les concepts d\'<b>historique</b>, de <b>plans</b> et de <b>règles</b>:</string>
  <string name="help_logs_plans_rules_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="There are three kinds of data structures:">Il y a trois types de structure de données:</string>
  <string name="help_import_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="A good starting point are some preconfigured rule sets available on the website. Just import them via import menu and play around.">Un bon départ peut consister à importer des jeux de règles préconfigurées disponibles sur le site internet et de jouer avec.</string>
  <string name="help_export_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="If you managed to set up a common plan for your country, do not hesitate to export your rule set to me by mail. I will put it on the website to make it available for all the users.">Si vous arrivez à définir un plan valable dans votre pays, n\'hésitez pas à m\'envoyer ces règles par mail. Je pourrai ainsi les rendre accessibles pour tous les utilisateurs.</string>
  <string name="help_logs_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; to save informations about your calls, messages and traffic statistics."><b>l\'historique (logs)</b> sauvegarde des informations sur vos appels, vos messages et l\'internet mobile,</string>
  <string name="help_plans_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Plans&lt;/b&gt; to describe all kinds of aspects of your bill."><b>les plans</b> pour décrire tous les aspects de votre facturation mobile,</string>
  <string name="help_rules_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Rules&lt;/b&gt; to match the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a particular &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;."><b> les règles</b> pour associer les <b>logs</b> à un <b>plan</b> particulier.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail0_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="You can add or delete &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; just as you want. You can set the order by dragging them around with the handle on the right of the list view.">Vous pouvez ajouter ou supprimer des <b>plans</b> comme vous le voulez. Vous pouvez changer leur ordre en les déplaçant par appui sur la droite de la liste.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail1_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice kurz &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="To edit a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;, you just need to click it. At the next screen, you can set all kind of settings. There are a few, most users won\'t need. But some do. A short help for each setting is displayed in this view. Most settings you do not understand are not used in your country. Just leave them as they are. ;)">Pour éditer un <b>plan</b>, vous n\'avez qu\'à appuyer dessus. Sur l\'écran suivant, vous pouvez modifier différents paramètres, dont certains ne seront pas utiles à la majorité des utilisateurs. Une aide rapide pour chaque paramètre est affichée dans cette vue. Les paramètres que vous ne comprenez pas ne sont pas utlisés dans votre pays : laissez les tel quels ;).</string>
  <string name="help_plans_merge_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice kurz &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="You can merge &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; to aggregate their &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; to a combined cost and limit.">Vous pouvez fusionner des <b>plans</b> pour obtenir des coûts/limites globales sur l\'ensemble de leurs <b>logs</b>.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail0_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice kurz &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="Edit the &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt; in the same way. Each &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; does match some &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; in which the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; should be billed in.">Editez les <b>règles</b> de la même façon. Chaque <b>règle</b> associe un ensemble de <b>logs</b> à un <b>plan</b> pour permettre la facturation de ces <b>logs</b> .</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail1_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice kurz &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="But keep in mind, that order is important for &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Gardez à l\'esprit que l\'ordre est important pour les <b>règles</b> :</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail2_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice kurz &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; are matched &lt;b&gt;top-down&lt;/b&gt;, means: the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; that matches will stop processing of this particular &lt;b&gt;log item&lt;/b&gt;.">Les <b>logs</b> sont traités de <b>haut en bas</b> : un &lt;log&gt; ne sera traité que par la première <b>règle</b>  qui le concerne.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail3_" formatted="false" username="Fabrice kurz &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="E.g.: If you match all calls to 0800% numbers to a \&quot;free\&quot; &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; with the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt;, there is no need to exclude these numbers in the second.">Par exemple, si vous associez tous les numéros en 0800% à un <b>plan</b> "gratuit" par la première <b>règle</b>, il n\'y a pas besoin d\'exclure ces numéros dans les suivantes.</string>
</resources>
