<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2012 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter NG. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/fr/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/">N\'hésitez pas à nous aider en traduisant cette application via le lien suivant: http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/</string>
  <string name="market_keywords" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="Keywords: minutes calls sms txt text data traffic counter log phone usage watchdog alert widget statistics at&amp;t verizon three o2 t-mobile vodafone orange">mots-clés : minutes appels sms txt text data traffic compteur log mobile utilisation alerte widget statistiques at</string>
  <string name="market_permissions" formatted="false" username="Fabrice KURZ &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="Permissions of this app:\n* READ SMS OR MMS: count your messages\n* RECEIVE SMS: update logs before a recently received message got deleted\n* FULL INTERNET ACCESS: importing rules\n* READ CONTACT DATA: convert numbers to names (e.g. in number groups)\n* MODIFY/DELETE SD CARD CONTENTS: write/export rules to sd card\n* READ PHONE STATE AND IDENTITY: update logs in background\n* PREVENT DEVICE FROM SLEEPING: update logs in background">Permissions pour cette application : \n* LECTURE SMS OU MMS : compte vos messages\n* RECEPTION SMS : mise-à-jour de l\'historique avant qu\'un nouveau message ne soit effacé\n* ACCES INTERNET COMPLET : importer des règles\n* DONNÉES DES CONTACTS : conversion des numéros en nom\n* MODIFIER/EFFACER LE CONTENU CARTE SD : écriture/export des règles sur carte SD\n* LECTURE DE L\'ÉTAT DU MOBILE : mise à jour des logs en arrière plan\n* EMPÊCHER LA MISE EN VEILLE : mise à jour des logs en arrière plan</string>
  <string name="market_cm2" formatted="false" username="Fabrice kurz &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="This is a complete rebuild of Call Meter NG. It has a huge amount of new features like widgets and alerts.\nIt\'s new architecure allows more complex plans.\nFeel free to test it and help me make it more userfriendly as it is currently. ;)">C\'est une nouvelle version de Call Meter NG. Il y a un nombre élevé de nouvelles fonctionnalités comme les widgets et les alertes.\nSa nouvelle architecture permet de créer des plans plus complexes.\nN\'hésitez pas à la tester et à m\'aider à la rendre plus agréable ;)</string>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" username="Fabrice kurz &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in market won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website.">Cette appli est un logiciel libre, conçu pendant mon temps libre. Donner de mauvais commentaires sur google play ne va pas la rendre meilleure.\nVeuillez SVP m\'informer des éventuels problèmes avec cette appli sur son site web.</string>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" username="Fabrice kurz &lt;kurzf@voila.fr&gt;" orig="Call Meter lets you keep an eye on your mobile plans.\n\nIt shows statistics of your calls/sms/txt/data traffic and lets you set limits for each of these plans.\nCall Meter supports a huge amount of billing modes to let you adapt it\'s behaviour to your operators billing.">Call meter vous permets de garder un oeil sur vos facture de téléphonie mobile.\n\nElle montre des statistiques sur vos appels/sms/internet et vous permet de définir des limites pour chaque type.\nCall Meter supporte un large éventail de modes de facturation pour vous adapter à votre opérateur.</string>
</resources>
