<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2012 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/nl/intro.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="intro_" formatted="false" username="Gummie" orig="Introducing Call Meter 3G">Introductie Call Meter 3G</string>
  <string name="intro0" formatted="false" username="Gummie" orig="With &lt;b&gt;Call Meter 3G&lt;/b&gt; you can monitor the usage of your calls, messages and data connections.">Met <b>Call Meter 3G</b> kan je het gebruik van je gespreks, berichten en data connecties in de gaten houden</string>
  <string name="intro1" formatted="false" username="Gummie" orig="In order to get accurate statistics, it is important to accurately set Call Meter 3G as they will be billed.">Om accurate statistieken te krijgen is het belangrijk om Call Meter 3G precies zo in te stellen zoals er gefactureerd wordt.</string>
  <string name="intro_simple" formatted="false" username="Gummie" orig="Most users need only set their settings in menu &lt;b&gt;Basic settings&lt;/b&gt;. Just set the number of inclusive minutes or messages, as well as adjust the cost of calls made, etc..">De meeste gebruikers hebben genoeg aan de instelling in het menu <b>Basis instellingen</b>. Stel alleen het aantal belminuten of berichten wat binnen de bundel valt in. En stel daarnaast ook de kosten van de gemaakte gesprekken, etc.. goed in.</string>
  <string name="intro_kill" formatted="false" username="Gummie" orig="Please note that &lt;b&gt;killing&lt;/b&gt; the app can lead to corrupted (data) statistics.">Let op dat het <b>killen</b> van de app leidt tot incorrecte (data) statistieken.</string>
  <string name="intro_data" formatted="false" username="Gummie" orig="Please note that no data statistics from before the last phone boot can be displayed.">Let op dat er geen data statistieken getoond kunnen worden voor het moment dat de telefoon opnieuw gestart is.</string>
  <string name="intro_import" formatted="false" username="Gummie" orig="If your billing is more complex, for example because messages and calls are billed as merged units, you can import pre-configured rules. Just select the menu &lt;b&gt;Import rule set&lt;/b&gt;.">Als je facturatie complex  is, bijvoorbeeld omdat de berichten en de gesprekken in de facturatie worden samengevoegd als een. Dan kan je de voor geconfigureerde regels importeren. Selecteer dan het in menu <b>Importeer regelset</b>.</string>
  <string name="intro_export" formatted="false" username="Gummie" orig="In any case, when everything is set up, you can export your rules to me. Thus, all other users can benefit from your work.">Je kan als alles is ingeregeld de regels exporteren en naar mij sturen. Op deze manier kunnen ook andere gebruikers profiteren van je werk.</string>
  <string name="intro_recalc1" formatted="false" username="Gummie" orig="The process can be greatly accelerated by the setting &lt;b&gt;Beginning of recording&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;Delete logs older than&lt;/b&gt;.">De voortgang kan erg versneld worden door de instelling <b>Begin van archief</b> of <b>Verwijder logs ouder dan</b>.</string>
  <string name="intro_recalc0" formatted="false" username="Gummie" orig="The statistics are recalculated after each change to the configuration. This will take some time depending on the number of calls or messages and used phone. It therefore makes sense to adjust all the settings possible in one fell swoop.">De statistieken zullen na elke configuratie wijziging worden herberekend.Dit kost wat tijd, afhankelijk van het aantal gesprekken of berichten en telefoongebruik. Het is daarom handig om alle instellingen in een keer goed te zetten.</string>
</resources>
