<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
       <!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2011 Felix Bechstein
       -->
       <!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
       <!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
      <!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/edit.php?lang=it&file=help.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="help_title_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="Please read the following to understand the concept of &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Per favore leggi qui per comprendere il concetto di &lt;b&gt;registri&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;piani&lt;/b&gt; e &lt;b&gt;regole&lt;/b&gt;:</string>
  <string name="help_import_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="A good starting point are some preconfigured rule sets available on the website. Just import them via import menu and play around.">Per iniziare ci sono alcuni set di regole preconfigurati disponibili sul sito. Importali tramite il menù e inizia a dare un\'occhiata.</string>
  <string name="help_export_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="If you managed to set up a common plan for your country, do not hesitate to export your rule set to me by mail. I will put it on the website to make it available for all the users.">Se hai impostato correttamente un piano diffuso nel tuo paese, non esitare ad esportare le tue regole e inviarle a me via mail. Le metterò sul sito, a disposizione a tutti gli utenti.</string>
  <string name="help_logs_plans_rules_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="There are three kinds of data structures:">Ci sono tre tipi di strutture dati:</string>
  <string name="help_logs_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; to save informations about your calls, messages and traffic statistics.">&lt;b&gt;registri&lt;/b&gt;: conservano le informazione sulle statistiche di chiamate, messaggi e traffico dati</string>
  <string name="help_plans_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="&lt;b&gt;Plans&lt;/b&gt; to describe all kinds of aspects of your bill.">&lt;b&gt;piani&lt;/b&gt;: descrivono tutte i dettagli della tua tariffa</string>
  <string name="help_rules_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="&lt;b&gt;Rules&lt;/b&gt; to match the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a particular &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;.">&lt;b&gt;regole&lt;/b&gt;: si applicano ai &lt;b&gt;registri&lt;/b&gt; e li assegnano a un particolare &lt;b&gt;piano&lt;/b&gt;</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail0_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="You can add or delete &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; just as you want. You can set the order by dragging them around with the handle on the right of the list view.">Puoi aggiungere o eliminare &lt;b&gt;piani&lt;/b&gt; a tuo piacimento. Puoi impostare l\'ordine trascinandoli con il selettore a destra della lista.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail1_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="To edit a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;, you just need to click it. At the next screen, you can set all kind of settings. There are a few, most users won\'t need. But some do. A short help for each setting is displayed in this view. Most settings you do not understand are not used in your country. Just leave them as they are. ;)">Per modificare un &lt;b&gt;piano&lt;/b&gt; devi semplicemente cliccarci su. Alla schermata seguente puoi definire tutte le impostazioni. Viene mostrata una breve guida per ciascuna impostazione.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_merge_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="You can merge &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; to aggregate their &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; to a combined cost and limit.">Puoi unire i &lt;b&gt;piani&lt;/b&gt; per aggregare gli &lt;b&gt;elementi registro&lt;/b&gt; a dei costi e limiti combinati.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail0_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="Edit the &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt; in the same way. Each &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; does match some &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; in which the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; should be billed in.">Modifica le &lt;b&gt;regole&lt;/b&gt; allo stesso modo. Ogni &lt;b&gt;regola&lt;/b&gt; si applica ad alcuni &lt;b&gt;elementi registro&lt;/b&gt; e li sposta in un &lt;b&gt;piano&lt;/b&gt; in cui i &lt;b&gt;registri&lt;/b&gt; devono essere tariffati.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail1_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="But keep in mind, that order is important for &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Ricorda che l\'ordine è fondamentale per le &lt;b&gt;regole&lt;/b&gt;:</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail2_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; are matched &lt;b&gt;top-down&lt;/b&gt;, means: the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; that matches will stop processing of this particular &lt;b&gt;log item&lt;/b&gt;.">I &lt;b&gt;registri&lt;/b&gt; vengono controllati &lt;b&gt;top-down&lt;/b&gt;, dall\'alto al basso: la prima &lt;b&gt;regola&lt;/b&gt; applicata blocca il controllo di quel particolare &lt;b&gt;elemento registro&lt;/b&gt;</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail3_" formatted="false" username="fireb33" orig="E.g.: If you match all calls to 0800% numbers to a \&quot;free\&quot; &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; with the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt;, there is no need to exclude these numbers in the second.">Es.: se tu assegni tutte le chiamate ai numeri 800% a un &lt;b&gt;piano&lt;/b&gt; "gratis" con la prima &lt;b&gt;regola&lt;/b&gt;, non serve escludere questi numeri nella seconda.</string>
</resources>
