<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
       <!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2015 Felix Bechstein
       -->
       <!--
               This file is part of Call Meter NG. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
       <!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
      <!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm2/nb/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" username="&quot;Olav&quot; &lt;olav@ogk.no&gt;" orig="Call Meter lets you keep an eye on your mobile plans.\n\nIt shows statistics of your calls/sms/txt/data traffic and lets you set limits for each of these plans.\nCall Meter supports a huge amount of billing modes to let you adapt it\'s behaviour to your operators billing.">Call Meter lar deg følge med på mobiltrafikken din.\n\nDen viser statistikk for samtaler/sms/datatrafikk og lar deg sette grenser for hver av disse.\n\nCall Meter støtter mange forskjellige takseringstyper og kan tilpasses din operatørs abonnementer.</string>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" username="&quot;Olav&quot; &lt;olav@ogk.no&gt;" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in market won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website.">Denne applikasjonen er åpen kildekode laget på fritiden. Negative kommentarer i Android Market hjelper ikke til å gjøre den bedre. Vær så snill å beskrive problemene du har med applikasjonen på Call Meters hjemmeside.</string>
  <string name="market_cm3" formatted="false" username="&quot;Olav&quot; &lt;olav@ogk.no&gt;" orig="There is a complete rebuild Call Meter 3G available in market. It has a huge amount of new features like widgets and alerts.\nIt\'s new architecure allows more complex plans.\nFeel free to test it and help me make it more userfriendly as it is currently. ;)">Det er en ny, helt omskrevet utgave kalt Call Meter 3G tilgjengelig i Android Market. Den har mange nye funksjoner som moduler (widgets) og varslinger, og ny arkitektur muliggjør mer komplekse takseringstyper/planer.\nPrøv den gjerne, og hjelp meg gjøre den mer brukervennlig enn den er i dag ;)</string>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" username="&quot;Olav&quot; &lt;olav@ogk.no&gt;" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: http://ub0r.de/translate/cm2/">Hjelp gjerne til med å oversette applikasjonen til ditt språk her: http://ub0r.de/translate/cm2/</string>
</resources>
