<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2013 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/es/intro.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="intro_" formatted="false" username="jonaguera" orig="Introducing Call Meter 3G">Presentación de Call Meter 3G</string>
  <string name="intro0" formatted="false" username="kaixer &lt;kaixer@gmx.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Call Meter 3G&lt;/b&gt; monitors usage of your calls, messages and data connections."><b>Call Meter 3G</b> monitoriza tu gasto en llamadas, mensajes de texto y tráfico de datos.</string>
  <string name="intro1" formatted="false" username="kaixer &lt;kaixer@gmx.com&gt;" orig="In order to get accurate statistics, it is important to set up Call Meter 3G as accurately as possible.">Para obtener unas estadísticas precisas, es importante configurar Call Meter 3G con la mayor exactitud posible.</string>
  <string name="intro_simple" formatted="false" username="kaixer &lt;kaixer@gmx.com&gt;" orig="Most users only need to set their settings in menu &lt;b&gt;Basic settings&lt;/b&gt;. Just set the number of inclusive minutes or messages. Set up cost for calls made, etc..">La mayor parte de los usuarios solo necesitan configurar sus opciones en el menú <b>Preferencias simples</b>. Simplemente establece el número de minutos o mensajes incluidos, así como el coste de las llamadas, etc..</string>
  <string name="intro_import" formatted="false" username="jonaguera" orig="If your billing is more complex, for example because messages and calls are billed as merged units, you can import pre-configured rules. Just select the menu &lt;b&gt;Import rule set&lt;/b&gt;.">Si tu facturación es más compleja, por ejemplo debido a que los mensajes y las llamadas se facturan conjuntamente, puedes importar reglas pre-configuradas. Utiliza para ello el menú <b>Importar conjunto de reglas</b>.</string>
  <string name="intro_export" formatted="false" username="jonaguera" orig="In any case, when everything is set up, you can export your rules to me. Thus, all other users can benefit from your work.">En cualquier caso, cuando todo esté configurado, puedes enviarme tus reglas. De este modo, los demás usuarios pueden beneficiarse de tu trabajo.</string>
  <string name="intro_recalc0" formatted="false" username="kaixer &lt;kaixer@gmx.com&gt;" orig="The statistics are recalculated after each change to the configuration. This will take some time depending on the number of calls, messages or data logs. It therefore makes sense to adjust all the settings in one fell swoop.">Las estadísticas se recalculan después de cada cambio en la configuración. Esto tomará un poco de tiempo dependiendo del número de llamadas, mensajes y uso de datos. Por eso resulta más conveniente ajustar todas las opciones posibles de una sola vez.</string>
  <string name="intro_recalc1" formatted="false" username="kaixer &lt;kaixer@gmx.com&gt;" orig="The process can be greatly accelerated by the setting &lt;b&gt;Beginning of recording&lt;/b&gt; or &lt;b&gt;Delete logs older than&lt;/b&gt;.">El proceso puede acelerarse en gran medida mediante la opción <b>Inicio de registros</b> o <b>Borrar los registros anteriores a</b>.</string>
  <string name="intro_data" formatted="false" username="kaixer &lt;kaixer@gmx.com&gt;" orig="Please note that no data statistics from before the last phone boot can be displayed.">Por favor, ten en cuenta que no pueden mostrarse datos estadísticos anteriores al último arranque del teléfono.</string>
  <string name="intro_kill" formatted="false" username="jonaguera" orig="Please note that &lt;b&gt;killing&lt;/b&gt; the app can lead to corrupted (data) statistics.">Por favor, ten en cuenta que <b>matar</b> la aplicación puede llevar a datos estadísticos corruptos.</string>
</resources>
