<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
    <!--
        Copyright (C) 2009-2015 Felix Bechstein
    -->
    <!--
        This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you
        can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU
        General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation;
        either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later
        version.
    -->
    <!--
        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
        WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
        MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
        General Public License for more details. You should have received a
        copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
        not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
    -->
<resources>
    <string formatted="false" name="intro_">Introducing Call Meter 3G</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="intro0"><b>Call Meter 3G</b> monitors usage of your calls, messages and data connections.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="intro1">In order to get accurate statistics, it is important to set up Call Meter 3G as accurately as possible.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="intro_simple">Most users only need to set their settings in menu <b>Basic settings</b>. Just set the number of inclusive minutes or messages. Set up cost for calls made, etc..</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="intro_import">If your billing is more complex, for example because messages and calls are billed as merged units, you can import pre-configured rules. Just select the menu <b>Import rule set</b>.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="intro_export">In any case, when everything is set up, you can export your rules to me. Thus, all other users can benefit from your work.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="intro_recalc0">The statistics are recalculated after each change to the configuration. This will take some time depending on the number of calls, messages or data logs. It therefore makes sense to adjust all the settings in one fell swoop.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="intro_recalc1">The process can be greatly accelerated by the setting <b>Beginning of recording</b> or <b>Delete logs older than</b>.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="intro_data">Please note that no data statistics from before the last phone boot can be displayed.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="intro_kill">Please note that <b>killing</b> the app can lead to corrupted (data) statistics.</string>
</resources>
