<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2012 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/hr/help.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="help_title_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone@pu.gmail.com" orig="Please read the following to understand the concept of &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Molim Vas pročitajte slijedeće za razumijevanje koncepta od <b>izvještaji</b>, <b>planovi</b> i <b>pravila</b>:</string>
  <string name="help_import_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone@pu.gmail.com" orig="A good starting point are some preconfigured rule sets available on the website. Just import them via import menu and play around.">Dobra startna pozicija su već predkonfigurirana podešenja pravila dostupna na web stranici. Samo ih uvezite kroz izbornik uvoza i isprobajte.</string>
  <string name="help_export_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone@pu.gmail.com" orig="If you managed to set up a common plan for your country, do not hesitate to export your rule set to me by mail. I will put it on the website to make it available for all the users.">Ako uspijete postaviti plan za svoju državu, ne ustručavajte se eksportirati vaše postavke na moj mail. Ja ću ih staviti na moju web stranicu kako bi bile dostupne svim korisnicima.</string>
  <string name="help_logs_plans_rules_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone@pu.gmail.com" orig="There are three kinds of data structures:">Postoje tri vrste struktura podataka:</string>
  <string name="help_logs_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; to save informations about your calls, messages and traffic statistics."><b>Izvještaji</b> za čuvanje statističkih informacija o vašim pozivima, porukama i prometu.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Plans&lt;/b&gt; to describe all kinds of aspects of your bill."><b>Planovi</b> za opis svih vrsta aspekata vašeg računa.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Rules&lt;/b&gt; to match the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a particular &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;."><b>Pravila</b> za bolje slaganje sa <b>izvještajima</b> i premještanje posebno <b>plana</b>.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail0_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="You can add or delete &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; just as you want. You can set the order by dragging them around with the handle on the right of the list view.">Možete dodati ili obrisati <b>planove</b> kako želite. Možete postaviti redoslijed povlačenjem okolo rukovanjem na desnoj strani pogleda liste.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail1_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="To edit a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;, you just need to click it. At the next screen, you can set all kind of settings. There are a few, most users won\'t need. But some do. A short help for each setting is displayed in this view. Most settings you do not understand are not used in your country. Just leave them as they are. ;)">Za uređivanje <b>plana</b>, trebate samo kliknuti. Na slijedećem ekranu, možete postaviti sve vrste podešenja. Tu je par, većini korisnika neželjenih podešenja. Ali neki ih koriste. Kratka pomoć za svako podešenje je prikazana u ovom pregledu. Većina postavki koju ne razumijete ne koriste se u vašoj zemlji. Samo ih ostavite kakve jesu. ;)</string>
  <string name="help_plans_merge_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="You can merge &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; to aggregate their &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; to a combined cost and limit.">Možete spojiti <b>planove</b> za generiranje njihovih <b>izvještaja stavki</b> da kombiniraju cijenu i jedinice.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail0_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Edit the &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt; in the same way. Each &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; does match some &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; in which the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; should be billed in.">Uredite <b>planove</b> na isti način. Svaki <b>plan</b> se slaže sa nekim <b>izvještajem stavki</b> i njegovim micanjem u <b>plan</b> u kojem ja <b>izvještaju</b> trebao bi biti obračunat.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail1_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="But keep in mind, that order is important for &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Ali imajte na umu, da redoslijed je važan za <b>pravila</b>:</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail2_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; are matched &lt;b&gt;top-down&lt;/b&gt;, means: the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; that matches will stop processing of this particular &lt;b&gt;log item&lt;/b&gt;."><b>Izvještaji</b> se slažu <b>gore-dolje</b>, znači: prvo <b>pravilo</b> koje se slaže će zaustaviti procesiranje točno određene <b>izvještaja stavke</b>.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail3_" formatted="false" username="Grmone &lt;grmone.pu@gmail.com&gt;" orig="E.g.: If you match all calls to 0800% numbers to a \&quot;free\&quot; &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; with the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt;, there is no need to exclude these numbers in the second.">Npr.: Ako se slažu svi pozivi na 0800% brojeva na "besplatno" <b>plan</b> sa prvim <b>pravilom</b>, nema potrebe dodati iznimku za te brojeve u sekundama.</string>
</resources>
