<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2013 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/es/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" orig="Call Meter 3G is the most complete monitor app for your Android device: It monitors your calls, text messages and data usage.\n\nIt shows statistics of your usage and shows alerts if you reach your limit.\nThere are all kinds of widgets to show the most valuable statistics directly on the home screen.\n\nCall Meter 3G has a complex rule engine to let you set up the app exactly the way your provider writes your bills.\n\nKnown problems:\n* Viber calls are detected as standard calls. Please tell Viber to fix this.\n* Doesn\'t count properly data usage on some Samsung devices. This problem is based on Samsung\'s Android version and got fixed on most devices with some Android update." username="Jaime &lt;jaime@bustillo.com&gt;">Call Meter es la aplicación de monitorización mas completa para su dispositivo Android: Monitoriza sus llamadas, mensajes de texto y uso de datos\n\nMuestra las estadísticas de tráfico de sus llamadas/sms/txt/datos y le permite fijar límites para recibir una alerta para cada uno de estos planes.\n\nCall Meter soporta una gran cantidad de modos de facturación y le permite adaptar su comportamiento a la facturación de su operador.\n\nProblemas conocidos:\n* Las llamadas de Viber se detectan como llamadas estandar. Por favor, pida a Viber que lo arregle.\n* NO cuenta adecuadamente el uso de datos en algunos dispositivos Samsung. El problema esta en la versión de Android que usa Samsung y se arregla en muchos de los dispositivos al hacer un update de la versión de Android.</string>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in Play Store won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website." username="Jaime &lt;jaime@bustillo.com&gt;">Esta aplicación es de código abierto, desarrollada en tiempo libre. Agregar malos comentarios en el mercado no ayudará mucho a mejorarla.\nPor favor agregue sus problemas con esta aplicación en el sitio WEB de la APP.</string>
  <string name="market_cm2" formatted="false" username="Pamemuro@gmail.com" orig="This is a complete rebuild of Call Meter NG. It has a huge amount of new features like widgets and alerts.\nIt\'s new architecure allows more complex plans.\nFeel free to test it and help me make it more userfriendly as it is currently. ;)">Esta es una reconstrucción completa de Call Meter NG. Tiene una vasta cantidad de nuevas funciones como widgets y alertas.\nSu nueva arquitectura permite planes más complejos.\nSiéntase en libertad de probarla y ayudarme a hacerla más amigable de lo que es actualmente. ;)</string>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/" username="Jaime &lt;jaime@bustillo.com&gt;">Siéntase en libertad de ayudar a traducir esta aplicación en su propio idioma aquí: http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3</string>
  <string name="market_keywords" formatted="false" orig="Keywords: minutes calls sms txt text data traffic counter log phone usage watchdog alert widget statistics at&amp;t verizon three o2 t-mobile vodafone orange">Palabras clave: minutos llamadas sms txt text datos tráfico contador bitácora teléfono uso aleta widget estadísticas at&amp;t verizon three 02 t-mobile vodafone orange</string>
  <string name="market_permissions" formatted="false" username="lboullo0 &lt;lucasboullosa@yahoo.com.ar&gt;" orig="Permissions of this app:\n* READ SMS OR MMS: count your messages\n* RECEIVE SMS: update logs before a recently received message got deleted\n* FULL INTERNET ACCESS: importing rules\n* READ CONTACT DATA: convert numbers to names (e.g. in number groups)\n* MODIFY/DELETE SD CARD CONTENTS: write/export rules to sd card\n* READ PHONE STATE AND IDENTITY: update logs in background\n* PREVENT DEVICE FROM SLEEPING: update logs in background">Permisos que necesita esta aplicación:\n* LEER SMS o MMS: para contar los mensajes\n* RECIBIR SMS: para alctualizar los logs antes que un mensaje recientemente recibido sea eliminado\n* ACCESO COMPLETO A INTERNET: para importar reglas\n* LEER INFORMACION DE LOS CONTACTOS: para convertir números a nombres (ej: en grupos de números)\n* MODIFICAR/ELIMINAR CONTENIDO DE LA TARJETA SD: para escribir/exportar reglas a la tarjeta sd\n* LEER ESTADO DEL TELEFONO E IDENTIDAD: para actualizar los logs en segundo plano\n* IMPEDIR QUE EL DISPOSITIVO ENTRE EN MODO ESPERA: para actualizar los logs en segundo plano</string>
  <string name="market_website" formatted="false" username="ar2rin" orig="Please see https://code.google.com/p/callmeter/issues/list for issues and enhancement requests.">Visite https://code.google.com/p/callmeter/issues/list para problemas conocidos y solicitudes de mejoras</string>
  <string name="market_promo" formatted="false" username="ar2rin" orig="Never spend too much!">Nunca gaste demasiado!</string>
</resources>
