<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2013 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit https://crowdin.com/project/callmeter3g/invitesk/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" username="ManuelMigel &lt;manuel.migel@gmail.com&gt;" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in Play Store won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website.">Toto je open source aplikácia tvorená vo voľnom čase. Negatívny komentár na Markete aplikáciu nevylepší.\nProsím pridajte Váš problém na web stránke aplikácie.</string>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" orig="Call Meter 3G is the most complete monitor app for your Android device: It monitors your calls, text messages and data usage.\n\nIt shows statistics of your usage and shows alerts if you reach your limit.\nThere are all kinds of widgets to show the most valuable statistics directly on the home screen.\n\nCall Meter 3G has a complex rule engine to let you set up the app exactly the way your provider writes your bills.\n\nKnown problems:\n* Viber calls are detected as standard calls. Please tell Viber to fix this.\n* Doesn\'t count properly data usage on some Samsung devices. This problem is based on Samsung\'s Android version and got fixed on most devices with some Android update." username="ManuelMigel &lt;manuel.migel@gmail.com&gt;">Call Meter Vám umožní mať Vaše mobilné účty pod dohľadom.\n\nZobrazuje štatistiku Vašich hovorov/SMS/MMS/dát a dovoľuje stanoviť limity pre každý typ.\nCall Meter podporuje širokú škálu účtovania, aby sa vedel prispôsobiť Vašim požiadavkám a spôsobu účtovania Vášho operátora.\n\nZnáme problémy:\n* Vıber hovory sú detekované ako bežné volania. Prosím, kontaktujte Viber pre opravu.\n* Nepočíta správne využitie dát na niektorých zariadeniach Samsung. Tento problém je len na niektorých verziách Androidu na zariadeniach Samsung a bol upravený na väčšine zariadení s nejakou aktualizáciu Android.</string>
  <string name="market_cm2" formatted="false" username="lenka lenka.casova@gmail.com sk" orig="This is a complete rebuild of Call Meter NG. It has a huge amount of new features like widgets and alerts.\nIt\'s new architecure allows more complex plans.\nFeel free to test it and help me make it more userfriendly as it is currently. ;)">Toto je kompletne prepísaný Call Meter NG. Má množstvo nových vlastností ako napr. wigety, či varovania.\nJeho nová architektúra dovoľuje oveľa komplexnejšie spôsoby tarifikácie.\nVyskúšajte ho a pomôžte ho spraviť ešte viac prívetivejším ako je. ;)</string>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" username="kayle.sk &lt;kayle.sk@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: https://crowdin.com/project/callmeter3g/invite">Môžete pomôcť aj s prekladom aplikácie na http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/</string>
  <string name="market_permissions" formatted="false" username="ManuelMigel &lt;manuel.migel@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Permissions of this app:\n* READ SMS OR MMS: count your messages\n* RECEIVE SMS: update logs before a recently received message got deleted\n* FULL INTERNET ACCESS: importing rules\n* READ CONTACT DATA: convert numbers to names (e.g. in number groups)\n* MODIFY/DELETE SD CARD CONTENTS: write/export rules to sd card\n* READ PHONE STATE AND IDENTITY: update logs in background\n* PREVENT DEVICE FROM SLEEPING: update logs in background">Povolenia tejto aplikácie:\n* ČÍTANIE SMS A MMS: počet správ\n* PRÍJEM SMS: aktualizácia protokolov nedávno prijatých správ pred ich odstránením\n* PLNÝ PRÍSTUP K INTERNETU: dodané pravidlá\n* ČÍTATA KONTAKTNÉ ÚDAJE: mení čísla na mená (napr. čísla skupín)\n* UPRAVUJE/MAŽE OBSAH SD KARTY: napísať/export pravidiel na SD kartu\n* ČÍTANIE IDENTITY A STAVU TELFÓNU: aktualizácia protokolov na pozadí\n* ZABRÁNENIE PRECHODU ZARIADENIA DO REŽIMU SPÁnKU: aktualizácia protokolov na pozadí</string>
  <string name="market_website" formatted="false" username="ManuelMigel &lt;manuel.migel@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Please see https://github.com/felixb/callmeter/issues for issues and enhancement requests.">Pozri https://github.com/felixb/callmeter/issues pre otázky a požiadavky na vylepšenie.</string>
  <string name="market_promo" formatted="false" username="ManuelMigel &lt;manuel.migel@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Never spend too much!">Nikdy neminiem viac!</string>
</resources>
