<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2012 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/ru/help.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="help_title_" formatted="false" username="flx &lt;f+translator@ub0r.de&gt;" orig="Please read the following to understand the concept of &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Пожалуйста, прочтите следующее, чтобы понять <b>журналы</b>, <b>планы</b> и <b>правила</b>:</string>
  <string name="help_logs_plans_rules_" formatted="false" username="Max &lt;s_live@list.ru&gt;" orig="There are three kinds of data structures:">Есть три вида структур данных:</string>
  <string name="help_import_" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="A good starting point are some preconfigured rule sets available on the website. Just import them via import menu and play around.">Хорошей отправной точкой являются некоторые предварительно настроенные наборы правил, доступные на веб-сайте. Просто импортируйте их через меню импорта и поиграйтесь с настройками.</string>
  <string name="help_logs_" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; to save informations about your calls, messages and traffic statistics."><b>Журналы</b> для сохранения информации о голосовых вызовах, сообщениях и передаче данных.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Plans&lt;/b&gt; to describe all kinds of aspects of your bill."><b>Планы</b> для описания всех аспектов вашей тарификации.</string>
  <string name="help_export_" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="If you managed to set up a common plan for your country, do not hesitate to export your rule set to me by mail. I will put it on the website to make it available for all the users.">Если вам удалось создать общий план для своей страны, не стесняйтесь, отправьте свой набор правил мне по электронной почте. Я выложу его на сайт, чтобы сделать доступным для всех пользователей.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail0_" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="You can add or delete &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; just as you want. You can set the order by dragging them around with the handle on the right of the list view.">Вы можете добавлять или удалять <b>планы</b> как пожелаете. Вы можете изменять порядок, перетаскивая их рукой в правой части списка.</string>
</resources>
