<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2012 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of Call Meter 3G. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/cm3/pl/help.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="help_title_" formatted="false" username="Mariusz &lt;mariusz.mb@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Please read the following to understand the concept of &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Proszę przeczytaj poniższe aby zrozumieć zasady <b>logów</b>, <b>planów</b> i <b>reguł</b>:</string>
  <string name="help_import_" formatted="false" username="Mariusz &lt;mariusz.mb@gmail.com&gt;" orig="A good starting point are some preconfigured rule sets available on the website. Just import them via import menu and play around.">Na początku możesz skorzystać ze wstępnie ustawionych reguł dostępnych na stronie internetowej. Po prostu zaimportuj je za pomocą menu import.</string>
  <string name="help_export_" formatted="false" username="Mariusz &lt;mariusz.mb@gmail.com&gt;" orig="If you managed to set up a common plan for your country, do not hesitate to export your rule set to me by mail. I will put it on the website to make it available for all the users.">Jeśli udało Ci się stworzyć plan dostępny w Twoim kraju, nie wahaj się wyeksportować go i przesłać do mnie za pomocą maila. Umieszczę go na stronie internetowej aby był dostępny dla wszystkich użytkowników.</string>
  <string name="help_logs_plans_rules_" formatted="false" username="Dariusz Więckiewicz &lt;dariusz@wieckiewicz.org&gt;" orig="There are three kinds of data structures:">Występują trzy rodzaje struktur danych:</string>
  <string name="help_plans_" formatted="false" username="Dariusz Więckiewicz &lt;dariusz@wieckiewicz.org&gt;" orig="&lt;b&gt;Plans&lt;/b&gt; to describe all kinds of aspects of your bill."><b>Plany</b> aby opisać wszystkie uwzględniane na twoim rachunku.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail0_" formatted="false" username="Dariusz Więckiewicz &lt;dariusz@wieckiewicz.org&gt;" orig="You can add or delete &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; just as you want. You can set the order by dragging them around with the handle on the right of the list view.">Możesz dodać lub usunąć <b>plany</b> tak jak chcesz. Możesz ustawić kolejność poprzez przeciągnięcie klikając za prawy róg w widoku listy.</string>
  <string name="help_plans_merge_" formatted="false" username="Dariusz Więckiewicz &lt;dariusz@wieckiewicz.org&gt;" orig="You can merge &lt;b&gt;plans&lt;/b&gt; to aggregate their &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; to a combined cost and limit.">Możesz scalić <b>plany</b> aby połączyć ich <b>elementy</b> w celu określenia łącznego kosztu i limitów.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail1_" formatted="false" username="Dariusz Więckiewicz &lt;dariusz@wieckiewicz.org&gt;" orig="But keep in mind, that order is important for &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt;:">Miej na uwadze, że kolejność jest ważna dla <b>reguł</b>:</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail3_" formatted="false" username="Dariusz Więckiewicz &lt;dariusz@wieckiewicz.org&gt;" orig="E.g.: If you match all calls to 0800% numbers to a \&quot;free\&quot; &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; with the first &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt;, there is no need to exclude these numbers in the second.">Np.: Jeżeli dopasujesz wszystkie połączenia do numeru 0800% do "darmowego" <b>planu</b> z pierwszą <b>regułą</b>, nie ma potrzeby wykluczać tych numerów w drugiej.</string>
  <string name="help_logs_" formatted="false" username="daniel@borek.me.uk" orig="&lt;b&gt;Logs&lt;/b&gt; to save informations about your calls, messages and traffic statistics."><b>Logi</b> aby zapisać informacje o statystykach Twoich rozmów, wiadomości i przesyłu danych.</string>
  <string name="help_rules_" formatted="false" username="daniel@borek.me.uk" orig="&lt;b&gt;Rules&lt;/b&gt; to match the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a particular &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;."><b>Reguły</b> dla <b>logów</b> potrzebne do uzycia ich z <b>planami</b></string>
  <string name="help_plans_detail1_" formatted="false" username="maladrill" orig="To edit a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt;, you just need to click it. At the next screen, you can set all kind of settings. There are a few, most users won\'t need. But some do. A short help for each setting is displayed in this view. Most settings you do not understand are not used in your country. Just leave them as they are. ;)">Aby edytować <b>plan</b> wystarczy go kliknąć. Na następnym ekranie można dokonać wyboru wszystkich ustawień. Jest też kilka, których większość użytkowników nie będzie potrzebować, ale niektórzy będą. W tym widoku będzie widoczna krótka pomoc dla każdego ustawienia. Większość ustawień, których nie rozumiesz nie jest używana w Twoim kraju. Zostaw je tak jak są. ;)</string>
  <string name="help_rules_detail0_" formatted="false" username="maladrill" orig="Edit the &lt;b&gt;rules&lt;/b&gt; in the same way. Each &lt;b&gt;rule&lt;/b&gt; does match some &lt;b&gt;log items&lt;/b&gt; and move them to a &lt;b&gt;plan&lt;/b&gt; in which the &lt;b&gt;logs&lt;/b&gt; should be billed in.">Edytuj <b>zasady</b> w ten sam sposób. Każda <b>zasada</b> pasuje do <b>elementów logu</b>, dlatego przenieś je do <b>planu</b> w którym <b>elementy</b> mają być zliczane.</string>
</resources>
